How to use fa430 to assemble code for 4e4th (*).  


fa430 is an assembler for MSP430 Code written in Win32Forth. This edition is made ​​especially for 4e4th. Copy & paste the output of fa430 in a file and download it to 4e4th.



Step by Step

Write you MSP430CODE in a source file. Any simple text file editor is ok for that. Read fa430-example-code-I.f and other example code files to learn how to do it.

Use win32forhIDE to open fa430.f and compile it.
The win32forth console will pop up ready to include your MSP43 code file.

fa430 will assemble your code, and output a script for 4e4th. The output skript has this form:

 HEX
 MSP430CODE <NAME>
 opcode i, opcode i,  opcode i,  ...
 END-CODE

Copy & paste it to a file. Then download that file to 4e4th.
Test your code with 4e4th.

If you have to verify code read the example files. You find methods there to do so.

Have fun.
mk 2013-01-20

---
(*) 4e4th: For education FORTH, on TI MSP430G2553 LaunchPad.
---

History

2013-01-23 mk
fa430 for win32forth_to_4e4th was build upon gforth version.
Its crosscompiler was tailored to produce a skript for 4e4th.

2011-06-12 mk
fa430 was made to provide an assembler for gforth-ec.
gforth version of fa430 has been verified:
$> gforth fa430.fs verify.fs -e bye > result.fs




